Frătean Tudor

Games Programmer

Cluj-Napoca, Romania cell: +40-752-222-995 fratean.tudor@gmail.com site: tudordot.com



First Chapter

A highly motivated and hardworking fast learner, with four years experience in game development across multiple platforms, looking to express my ideas and creativity in a new challenging environment. After implementing both engines and games, I hope to be able to learn, innovate, and leave a mark in this fast paced industry.

Skill List

Proficient in C++, C# / .NET with Unity, ActionScript 3.0, and Game Development on both PC and mobile.

Experienced in JavaScript, p5.js and CSS / HTML.

Knowledge of OpenGL, Java, SQL, Android, Bluetooth and Networking.

Previous Titles and Projects

Titles: tudordot.com/portfolio

Other Projects: tudordot.com/others

Employment History

Gameloft, Cluj-Napoca, 2017 - Present, Worked on engine development, gameplay programming and AI. I was the only programmer in a prototype phase then switched to an in-house C++ engine where I helped with bothgeneral programming and engine implementations.

Transylgamia, Cluj-Napoca, 2015 - 2016, Developed multiple games, both 2D and 3D, on Android and IOS using Unity and C#.

Idea Studios, Cluj-Napoca, year of 2014, Created Flash game engine for a rapid development team, with an outcome of 4 to 5 games per week. Helped and taught both interns and employees that were not accustomed with either OOP or graphic engines. Developed a game in Starling.

Education / Qualification

Babes-Bolyai University, Faculty of Mathematics and Computer Science, Cluj-Napoca, 2013-2016, Bachelor degree in Computer Science.

National College Emil Racovita, Cluj-Napoca, 2009-2013.

Nicolae Balcescu Lyceum, Cluj-Napoca, 2001-2009.

Cambridge ESOL Level Certificate in ESOL international, Certificate in Advanced English, 2011. Oracle Academy: Database Design and Programming With SQL Course, 2011.